<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AboutMe</string>
    <string name="name">Jiayi Su</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow star</string>
    <string name="bio">Hi, my name is Jiayi.
        \n\nI love <i>fish</i>.
        \n\nThe kind that is alive and swims around in an aquarium or river, or a lake, and definitely the ocean.
        \nFun fact is that I have several aquariums and also a river.
        \n\nI like eating fish, too. Raw fish. Grilled fish. Smoked fish. Poached fish - not so much.
        \nAnd sometimes I even go fishing.
        \nAnd even less sometimes, I actually catch something.
        \n\nOnce, when I was camping in Canada, and very hungry, I even caught a large salmon with my hands.
        \n\nI\'ll be happy to teach you how to make your own aquarium.
        \nYou should ask someone else about fishing, though.\n\n </string>
    <string name="bio1">A story about <i>fish</i>.
        \n\nOnce upon a time, there lived three fishes in a pond. They were close friends and were living together for years, in the same pond.
        \n\nOne day, a fisherman passing through the way saw that the pond was filled with fishes.
        \nHe was surprised and delighted, and immediately informed his fellows about it. Together, they decided to come the next morning and catch those fishes.
        \n\nOne of the three fishes, who was also the wisest, heard the conversation between the fisherman and his fellows.
        \nIt immediately rushed to the other two and explained them the entire situation, and also suggested that they leave the pond immediately and move to another place.
        \nThe second fish agreed and decided to move out from the pond quickly.
        \nThe third fish, however, mocked at them. He felt that the pond was their home, and they must not leave their home.
        \nSince the other two fishes were unable to convince the third fish, they left the pond and decided to let him follow his own course of action.
        \n\nThe next day, the fisherman and his fellows cast their nets and caught plenty of fishes.
        \nThey also managed to catch the third fish, who had refused to leave the pond, while the other two fishes, who left earlier, were saved..\n\n </string>
    <string name="black_white_map">Blak white map</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your Nickname?</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
</resources>
